Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration, 1910-1991; MS2142 Series 2; 18.5 Linear feet (Box 37, Box 38, Box 29, Box 31, Box 32, Box 30, Box 34, Box 33, Box 36, Box 35, Box 23, Box 22, Box 25, Box 24, Box 27, Box 26, Box 20, Box 28, Box 21, Box 16, Box 15, Box 18, Box 17, Box 12, Box 11, Box 14, Box 13, Box 8, Box 7, Box 10
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Administration, undated (Box 18)
  - Partial Index to subjects in the Board of Directors minutes and Neighborhood Advisory Council, 1960-1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Administration, undated (Box 19)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    (articles on Board members)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Article on board member, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Article on board members, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Article on board members, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Board of Directors meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Article on board member, undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Administration, undated (Box 20)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Administration, undated (Box 21)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Board of Directors meetings, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Administration, undated (Box 22)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Membership Committee members - information on members or prospective members, 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Committee Rosters, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Committee Rosters, 1940 ca. (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Committee Rosters, 1950 ca. (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Committee Rosters, 1960 ca. (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Committee Rosters, 1970 ca. (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Administration, undated (Box 23)
  - Committee on Committees, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Board and Staff Joint Committee, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws Committee, 1942-1956 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws Committee, 1942-1956 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Community Relations Committee, n.d., undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Executive Committee, 1970 ca. (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Administration, undated (Box 24)
  - Executive Coordinating Committee, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Executive and Finance Committee, 1944-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Executive and Finance Committee, 1944-1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Executive and Finance Committee, 1944-1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee, 1940 ca. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee, 1940 ca. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Finance Committee, 1940 ca. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Finance Committee, 1940 ca. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Finance Committee, 1940 ca. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Finance Committee, 1950 ca. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee, 1960 ca. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Finance and Program Committee, Finance and Program - Personnel Committee, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Foundation and Project Committee, 1956-1962 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Administration, undated (Box 25)